<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/3.3.1" created="2012-04-06 23:56" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.1/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.1/"
>

<channel>
	<title>ChapeauAgricuturalSociety.com</title>
	<link>http://chapeau.phpfogapp.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 23:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.1</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://chapeau.phpfogapp.com</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://chapeau.phpfogapp.com</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>wilk0146</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>wilk0146@algonquinlive.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[wilk0146]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>
	<wp:author><wp:author_id>2</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>vank0026</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>vank0026@algonquinlive.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[vank0026]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>
	<wp:author><wp:author_id>3</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>gite0002</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>gite0002@algonquinlive.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[gite0002]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[Priyanka]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Gite]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.3.1</generator>

	<item>
		<title>test minutes 1</title>
		<link>http://chapeau.phpfogapp.com/minutes/test-minutes-1/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 19:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>wilk0146</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chapeau.phpfogapp.com/?post_type=minutes&#038;p=802</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Its escape meant the utter ruin of our plan, and in all probability my instant death.  This thought lent wings to my feet; but even at my best I could do no more than hold my own with the leaping thing before me.</p>

<p>Of a sudden it turned into an apartment on the right of the corridor, and an instant later as I rushed in I found myself facing two of the Mahars.  The one who had been there when we entered had been occupied with a number of metal vessels, into which had been put powders and liquids as I judged from the array of flasks standing about upon the bench where it had been working.  In an instant I realized what I had stumbled upon.  It was the very room for the finding of which Perry had given me minute directions.  It was the buried chamber in which was hidden the Great Secret of the race of Mahars.  And on the bench beside the flasks lay the skin-bound book which held the only copy of the thing I was to have sought, after dispatching the three Mahars in their sleep.</p>

<p>There was no exit from the room other than the doorway in which I now stood facing the two frightful reptiles.  Cornered, I knew that they would fight like demons, and they were well equipped to fight if fight they must.  Together they launched themselves upon me, and though I ran one of them through the heart on the instant, the other fastened its gleaming fangs about my sword arm above the elbow, and then with her sharp talons commenced to rake me about the body, evidently intent upon disemboweling me.  I saw that it was useless to hope that I might release my arm from that powerful, viselike grip which seemed to be severing my arm from my body.  The pain I suffered was intense, but it only served to spur me to greater efforts to overcome my antagonist.</p>

<p>Back and forth across the floor we struggled&mdash;the Mahar dealing me terrific, cutting blows with her fore feet, while I attempted to protect my body with my left hand, at the same time watching for an opportunity to transfer my blade from my now useless sword hand to its rapidly weakening mate.  At last I was successful, and with what seemed to me my last ounce of strength I ran the blade through the ugly body of my foe.</p>

<p>Soundless, as it had fought, it died, and though weak from pain and loss of blood, it was with an emotion of triumphant pride that I stepped across its convulsively stiffening corpse to snatch up the most potent secret of a world.  A single glance assured me it was the very thing that Perry had described to me.</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>802</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2012-04-06 19:35:46</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2012-04-06 19:35:46</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>test-minutes-1</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>minutes</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="minutes"><![CDATA[Minutes]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>test minutes 2</title>
		<link>http://chapeau.phpfogapp.com/minutes/test-minutes-2/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 19:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>wilk0146</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chapeau.phpfogapp.com/?post_type=minutes&#038;p=803</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>He was overjoyed at seeing me, and to know the meaning of the fight, faint echoes of which had reached his prison cell.  He told me that the air patrol had captured him before he reached the high tower of the palace, so that he had not even seen Sab Than.</p>

<p>We discovered that it would be futile to attempt to cut away the bars and chains which held him prisoner, so, at his suggestion I returned to search the bodies on the floor above for keys to open the padlocks of his cell and of his chains.</p>

<p>Fortunately among the first I examined I found his jailer, and soon we had Kantos Kan with us in the throne room.</p>

<p>The sounds of heavy firing, mingled with shouts and cries, came to us from the city's streets, and Tars Tarkas hastened away to direct the fighting without.  Kantos Kan accompanied him to act as guide, the green warriors commencing a thorough search of the palace for other Zodangans and for loot, and Dejah Thoris and I were left alone.</p>

<p>She had sunk into one of the golden thrones, and as I turned to her she greeted me with a wan smile.</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>803</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2012-04-06 19:37:03</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2012-04-06 19:37:03</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>test-minutes-2</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>minutes</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="minutes"><![CDATA[Minutes]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>test minutes 3</title>
		<link>http://chapeau.phpfogapp.com/minutes/test-minutes-3/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 23:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>wilk0146</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chapeau.phpfogapp.com/?post_type=minutes&#038;p=820</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>"The harpoon is not yet forged that ever will do that," answered the other, sadly glancing upon a rounded hammock on the deck, whose gathered sides some noiseless sailors were busy in sewing together.</p>

<p>"Not forged!" and snatching Perth's levelled iron from the crotch, Ahab held it out, exclaiming&mdash;"Look ye, Nantucketer; here in this hand I hold his death! Tempered in blood, and tempered by lightning are these barbs; and I swear to temper them triply in that hot place behind the fin, where the White Whale most feels his accursed life!"</p>

<p>"Then God keep thee, old man&mdash;see'st thou that"&mdash;pointing to the hammock&mdash;"I bury but one of five stout men, who were alive only yesterday; but were dead ere night. Only THAT one I bury; the rest were buried before they died; you sail upon their tomb." Then turning to his crew&mdash;"Are ye ready there? place the plank then on the rail, and lift the body; so, then&mdash;Oh! God"&mdash;advancing towards the hammock with uplifted hands&mdash;"may the resurrection and the life&mdash;"</p>

<p>"Brace forward! Up helm!" cried Ahab like lightning to his men.</p>

<p>But the suddenly started Pequod was not quick enough to escape the sound of the splash that the corpse soon made as it struck the sea; not so quick, indeed, but that some of the flying bubbles might have sprinkled her hull with their ghostly baptism.</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>820</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2012-04-06 23:32:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2012-04-06 23:32:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>test-minutes-3</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>minutes</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
